we have yet to discover. Like that's what the market is telling you is that you kind of, you need your own framework, but in a 20 to 30 minute audition, all framework, no story, you know, forgive my language, but we didn't give a shit.
Your framework means nothing if we've not connected with you as a speaker first. And so people who've been in this space for a long time, it's like they, we get comfortable.
We rest on the laurels of kind of what worked yesterday or yesteryear.
And that has been one of the
biggest ways that I can add value They're already great speakers. It's how do we bring some of that kind of reinvention flair and some of your recent experiences and take what we know is already working and breathe new life into it.
Awesome. Ross, why don't you ask your question and then we'll go to Kimberly's question, both in the chat.
Sure. So Samantha, you, you were mentioning things like online courses and things like that. Um, with presumably doing that much business in, in the JVs, that is, there's time constraints to, to how much time you can offer.
How much of what you're doing is sort of the in-person, one-on-one kind of approach versus something that's asynchronous like a course or online material, something that someone can watch without you being there?
So I actually haven't created content for anyone else's, um, self-paced content, I should say, for anyone else's course. Anything that I've done now has been live, either in person or virtual.
Um, I haven't crossed that bridge yet into, you know, do we want to license some of my material for their courses or give them videos that they can use and integrate in um, like a self-paced learning experience.
So all of it has been my hour or hours going in. Um, that said, maybe I'll have a different tune next year, but because I haven't found a way yet for people to experience me not live and feel so excited about converting that it's in my best interest and I get most lit up and I'm able to
do my best work and walk away with the most opportunities when I go in to a live either workshop, conference, or virtual opportunity.
Great, thanks.
The more I do this job, the more I realize I'd rather have people read their own question because it humanizes the whole thing.
I don't feel right reading your questions, so I gotta break all the rules apart. Ross, I'm sorry.
Kimberly, there are rules. There are rules, apparently. I don't— I'm not living well by them. So Kimberly, why don't you ask your question?
Yeah, thank you. I just— I found your story so compelling, and I wanted to know what were your most difficult